Once upon a time,
there was a peaceful kingdom
ruled by a virtuous
queen and king.
More than anything,
they wished for a child.
One winter's night,
a blizzard swept through their
land,
blotting out the kingdom
in a bitter storm of snow and
ice,
but leaving them a
most precious gift.
A princess was born.
To honor the night she arrived,
her parents named
the girl Snow White.
As she grew,
the king and queen taught Snow
White
that the bounty of the land
belonged to all who tended it.
They showed her how
to rule with love.
For someday, her destiny
would be to lead.
♪ Look upon this land ♪
♪ On the home we've
come to know ♪
♪ Where magic and
light fill the air ♪
♪ Where we plant a tender seed ♪
♪ Trusting something
good will grow ♪
♪ A kingdom for the
free and the fair ♪
♪ Deep within the earth ♪
♪ There are wonders
to be found ♪
♪ In the fields
And the fruits that they bear ♪
♪ With a treasure
trove of gems ♪
♪ Hidden just below the ground ♪
♪ A beautiful
abundance we share ♪
♪ From the mountains high ♪
♪ To the deepest mines ♪
-♪ In a golden sky ♪
- ♪ How the kingdom shines ♪
♪ And we give to this land ♪
♪ With a generous hand ♪
♪ And the bounty will flow ♪
♪ Where the good things grow ♪
♪ Make a wish for
all you want to be ♪
♪ Tell us who you
someday wish to see ♪
Go on.
♪ All I see is water ♪
♪ A mother, father, daughter ♪
♪ And the seed of
someone who will lead ♪
♪ And make the
good things grow ♪
♪ Someone fearless ♪
♪ Someone fair ♪
♪ Someone brave ♪
♪ Someone true ♪
♪ Make a wish ♪
♪ And you will see her too ♪
♪ From the mountains high ♪
♪ To the deepest mines ♪
-♪ In a golden sky ♪
- ♪ How the kingdom shines ♪
♪ And we gather and give ♪
♪ As together we live ♪
♪ By the lessons we know ♪
♪ Where the good things grow ♪
Hi.
The king and queen
watched with pride
as Snow White grew
into a kind and fair young
princess.
But then, tragedy struck.
Snow White's mother fell ill.
And the Good Queen died.
Snow White and the
king were heartbroken.
Until...
an enchanting woman from a far
-off land appeared at the
palace.
So great was her
beauty that it seemed
to grant her powers
beyond the ordinary.
She married the king,
but she was not
what she appeared.
She was evil
and cared only
about her own beauty
and the power it granted.
To protect that power,
she kept a magic mirror
which could answer
but one simple question.
Magic Mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all?
You, my Queen,
of all the women reckoned fair,
your beauty is beyond compare.
The new queen wasted
no time seizing power.
She warned of a terrible threat
from beyond the Southern
Kingdom.
So the Good King swore
to defend his people.
♪ Hold it close ♪
♪ Til I return to you ♪
But the
king did not return.
Fear gripped the kingdom.
And the queen's power grew.
She turned the
farmers into soldiers
loyal only to her,
and robbed the riches of the
kingdom for herself.
She made Snow White a servant
and locked her away
behind the castle walls.
But as long as the mirror
answered the queen each day tht
she was the fairest,
Snow White remained safe
from the queen's cruel jealous.
♪ From the mountain high ♪
♪ To the deepest mine ♪
♪ Where's the golden sky? ♪
♪ Did it ever shine? ♪
♪ Was it beautiful then? ♪
♪ Will we find it again? ♪
♪ How I wish I could go ♪
As the years passed,
the people nearly forgot
there ever was a princess
named Snow White.
♪ Where the good things grow ♪
And in truth,
Snow White nearly
forgot herself.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
Is there something
I can help you with?
That's okay. Just browsing.
Well, I'm going to have to ask
you to put those back.
I would, but it seems like
the queen has plenty already.
Oh, I see.
So that's your excuse for
stealing?
My friends are hungry. I'm
hungry. That's my excuse.
Maybe I can speak
with the queen.
You really think the people
upstairs want to share with
people like us?
Well, the princess would.
Snow White.
Snow White hasn't been seen or
heard from in many years.
I doubt she'll be of
any help to anyone.
All she does is think of
how to help her people.
Well, then you should let her
know, at some point,
it might be useful for her
to stop thinking.
Maybe start doing.
There's an intruder in
the castle. Seal the doors!
Take some for yourself.
And share the rest
with your princess.
Maybe no one else
has even told her.
I'm sure if the queen was aware
of how desperate things have
gotten,
she would be happy to share.
I at least have to try,
even if it is just a wish.
Wish... Wish...
Wish...
Snow White, have you
finished your chores?
Yes, Your Majesty.
It's important we
all do our share.
Well, that's what I came
to speak to you about, actually.
Sharing.
Please.
You were saying?
It's just...
Your Majesty,
people are struggling,
and it may not be much,
but when I was young,
my parents and I would pick
apples.
We'd take them and make pies,
-then go out into the village...
-Pies?
Pies are luxuries.
They don't need luxuries.
It confuses them.
But sometimes something small,
something sweet even,
can make you believe that
there's more to being alive than
mere subsistence.
You know, I really don't
remember you being this...
opinionated.
My apologies. It's just...
I feel they need some kindness.
"Fearless, fair, brave, true."
How quaint.
One day, you'll understand
how useless those words are.
But in the meantime,
here's a tidbit for you.
Observe.
Ravishing, isn't it?
Yes, Your Majesty.
One is weak, useless, fragile.
The other hard, unyielding,
everlasting, flawless,
beautiful.
My subjects don't want a flower.
They want a diamond.
-Your Highness...
-Get your hands off me!
...this criminal was caught
in the scullery pilfering royal
supplies.
That's a lie.
Are you one of the bandits
that gather in the forest
stealing in the name of the
king?
No, no, Your Majesty.
Not "one of the
bandits." I'm the boss.
Loyal to the one true king.
Find his home and
burn it to the ground.
Funny thing is,
I don't actually have a home.
Then take him to the dungeon.
-Fill the castle with his cries.
-Your Majesty...
I understand the
need for justice.
But please, this isn't fair.
What did you say?
The punishment must
not exceed the crime,
- and I know my father would...
- Your father?
Your father?
My father would show mercy.
I'm sorry, my
dear. You're right.
This thief stole from me.
So, I will steal from him.
Remove his coat and boots
and bind him to the gates to
freeze.
You know, is the
dungeon still an option?
Take him away!
Wait, he'll perish.
Please, Your Majesty.
Snow White!
Here...
look at yourself.
Isn't this what you want?
Go on,
speak to your people.
Your subjects await
you, Snow White.
Your pies and your wise words.
What will you tell them, hmm?
That you've made them dessert?
You live in a world of wishes.
Go back to your
well, Snow White.
♪ Little girl at a lonely well ♪
♪ With the same
little tale to tell ♪
♪ Feeling trapped by the walls
That hold her ♪
♪ Feeling stuck in the story
They've told her ♪
♪ Another day where
she fades away ♪
♪ Never daring to disobey ♪
♪ So she's dreaming all alone ♪
♪ Sharing secrets
with the stone ♪
♪ My father told me, long ago ♪
♪ I braved a bitter
storm of snow ♪
♪ Is that a girl I'll
ever know again? ♪
♪ I'm waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Beneath a thousand treetops ♪
♪ And as the silver sky stops ♪
♪ I send a whisper
to the water ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Holding out for someday ♪
♪ Hoping somehow, some way ♪
♪ I'll become my
father's daughter ♪
♪ I close my eyes and see ♪
♪ The girl I'm meant to be ♪
♪ Is she a part of me
I've yet to find? ♪
♪ Wondering, "Will
she appear?" ♪
♪ Or will I be forever here ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish? ♪
♪ Little girl by a wild wood ♪
♪ How she tries to
be someone good ♪
♪ But in the shadow
The kingdom's caught in ♪
♪ Somehow fairness
is long forgotten ♪
♪ So will she rise
or bow her head? ♪
♪ Will she lead
or just be led? ♪
♪ Is she the girl
She always said she'd be? ♪
♪ I'm waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Beneath a thousand treetops ♪
♪ And as the silver sky stops ♪
♪ I long to leave
the walls behind me ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Holding out for someday ♪
♪ Hoping somehow, some way ♪
♪ There comes a
miracle to find me ♪
♪ I close my eyes and see ♪
♪ The girl I'm meant to be ♪
♪ Is she a part of me
I've had to hide? ♪
♪ Wondering, "Will
she appear?" ♪
♪ Or will I spend another year ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish? ♪
♪ They say all you have to do ♪
♪ To make your wish come true ♪
♪ Is let it echo,
echo, echo, echo ♪
♪ Your voice will
carry through ♪
♪ And bring that dream to you ♪
♪ Just like an
echo, echo, echo ♪
♪ Well, I can hear the echo
Loud and clear ♪
♪ But I'm still waiting here ♪
Come on! Move it!
Move!
Shut up!
It isn't much, but...
Tell me what it's
like out there.
Why don't you come and find out?
I can't.
I saw you give it to
the queen back there.
You seem brave enough.
Brave?
You have to go. Run.
-Thank you.
-Go.
♪ Waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Beyond a whisper
to the water ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish ♪
♪ Is it almost someday? ♪
♪ Can I somehow, some way ♪
♪ Learn to be my
father's daughter? ♪
♪ Someone who could
fin'lly start ♪
♪ Start speaking with
a fearless heart ♪
♪ Someone who just
might be brave ♪
♪ Someone no one needs to save ♪
♪ Well, I can always dream ♪
♪ But then... ♪
♪ I wake up and it's me again ♪
♪ Waiting on a wish ♪
Magic Mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all?
Famed is thy beauty, Majesty.
But wait,
a lovely maiden I now behold
awakened to the world.
Nothing can hide
her gentle grace,
for I see
she is more fair than thee.
No!
Huntsman?
Your Majesty.
Take Snow White far
into the forest.
Find a secluded glade
where she can pick apples,
and there,
my faithful Huntsman,
kill her.
But,
Majesty,
she's just a girl.
And I'm your queen.
It was Snow White who
set the bandit free.
She's plotting against me.
Now, tell me,
are you against me, too?
Are you? Yes or no?
No,
Majesty.
Take
her to the forest.
Kill her.
Cut out her heart.
Put it in this box.
On your return,
you will have anything
your heart desires.
Would you like one?
You're very kind.
It's getting late.
Why?
You must flee into the woods.
The queen is mad.
She'll stop at nothing.
I can't leave the kingdom.
She is evil, child.
She's a liar.
You were never told the truth
about your father.
Go!
-But what about my father?
-Go. Please!
Before I change my mind!
Go!
Hello?
Is there anybody here?
♪ Heigh-ho ♪
-♪ Heigh-ho ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho
It's off to work we go ♪
♪ It's rise and shine ♪
♪ And stay in line! ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho, heigh-ho
Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ We heard the rooster crow ♪
♪ All dressed and fed ♪
♪ Full speed ahead ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
- ♪ A splendid day to say ♪
-♪ Achoo! ♪
-Oh, my!
-Gesundheit.
Why, thank you.
♪ Do ya know what
I'm allergic to? ♪
♪ This sorry sack of chumps ♪
♪ Ah, why don't you
shut it, Grumps! ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho
Heigh-ho, heigh-hum ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ It's off to work we go ♪
♪ I function best on
a full night's rest ♪
♪ And so, it's
back to bed I go ♪
Hello?
♪ I'm sleepy ♪
♪ Yeah, we know! ♪
♪ And the more we talk
The less we walk ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Heigh-ho ♪
♪ Deep in the dark ♪
♪ Our magic will mark
A spot where the sparkle starts
to shine ♪
♪ There's gems in the land
So hold up your hand ♪
♪ As light so brightly
fills the mine ♪
-♪ Now quick, better climb 'n
dig ♪ -♪ For a diamond ♪
♪ Get your rear in gear ♪
♪ Now yank up your socks ♪
♪ Let's rip at the rocks ♪
♪ And as we swing ♪
♪ We always sing ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ The highest high I know ♪
♪ Is when we dig
Up rocks this big ♪
♪ And so
My smile starts to grow ♪
- ♪ I glow! ♪
- Ugh!
-♪ I'm happy! ♪
-♪ Yeah, we know! ♪
♪ You make me sick
A bucket, quick! ♪
♪ Uh-oh! ♪
♪ Heigh-ho ♪
♪ We dig, dig, dig, dig, dig,
dig Dig from early morn till
night ♪
♪ We dig, dig, dig, dig, dig,
dig Dig up everything in sight♪
♪ We dig up diamonds
by the score ♪
♪ A thousand rubies ♪
♪ Sometimes more! ♪
♪ It's the sparkly stuff
we're digging for ♪
♪ We dig, dig, dig-a-dig, dig ♪
♪ Heigh-ho ♪
-♪ Heigh-ho ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ It's home from work we go ♪
♪ Day's over, gang! ♪
-♪ We're done? ♪
-♪ Hot dang! ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
♪ Sing out, fortissimo ♪
♪ Oh, dear, oh, my ♪
♪ Do you mind if I lay low ♪
♪ See, sometimes I get so...
Get so... ♪
-♪ He's bashful! ♪
-♪ Yeah, we know! ♪
♪ Well, move your tail
Let's hit the trail ♪
♪ Don't drag your feet ♪
♪ It's time to eat! ♪
-♪ We'll sleep ♪
-♪ Amen! ♪
♪ Arise and then ♪
♪ It's off to work we go again ♪
♪ Heigh-ho ♪
-♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho ♪
-♪ Heigh-ho ♪
♪ Heigh-ho, heigh-ho! ♪
- Easy with that door,
Doc.
Home sweet home.
It is indeed exceptional
to be back at our place of
habitation.
Is it me or
is it dusty in here?
It's you.
Can't wait to floss.
It's a... It's a...
It's a...
What?
He did it again.
Narcoleptic cataplexy.
I thought he just...
fell asleep when he was worried.
What's there to
be worried about?
Time to worry!
Barricade the door!
Guys, where's Dopey?
Don't move.
Ogres smell fear.
It's not an ogre. It's a
phantasm.
Should he
crouch and hide?
Or make himself big and roar?
Depends what kind of ogre.
It's not an ogre!
It's a demon goat.
Don't look
it in the eyes.
If you see ectoplasm,
- don't touch it.
- Is it floating?
Be careful, Dopey.
Don't be afraid.
It's all right.
I only wanted to meet you.
What's your name?
Don't you speak?
Let's take
back our friend!
Wait, wait. Please.
-Why...
-It's a human.
Well, yes. What did
you think I was?
-Nothing.
-Ghost.
- But where did you come from?
- Are you hungry?
Can we be friends?
What's your name?
Why is everyone
being so cordial?
The only human things that come
into the forest anymore are
bandits
-who claim to fight in the
king's name. -What?
You're in trouble with
the law, aren't ya?
Hmm?
-I'd better go.
-Told ya.
- No, no, no. Wait, wait. Hold
on. - Let her leave.
Well, at least tell
us who you are.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
My name is Snow White.
- Snow White?
- The princess?
I say it's a trap.
But she needs our help.
- Anyone still think
she's a ghost? -Wait, wait,
wait. Where are you going?
As far away from the
castle as possible.
- That's not good
enough. - But why?
The truth is, the
queen tried to kill me.
She really tried to kill you?
Well, that's terrible.
It's also exactly why
you have to leave.
You should stay here until you
figure out where you're gonna
go.
-What?
-I think that's a wonderful
idea.
Now, hold on.
A human shows up in this cottage
for the first time
in 275 years
and you ask her to stay?
Did he just say
275 years?
274, to be precise.
We're as old as the trees.
My parents always said
this forest was a magical place.
And I've always said
that humans cause nothing but
trouble.
I'm sorry. I don't
know your name.
Allow me to introduce
in alphabetical order.
Bashful. Dopey.
Grumpy. Happy.
Sleepy. Sneezy.
And I'm Doc.
You said we were doing
reverse alphabetical order this
time.
That was last time.
So, in reverse order,
it's Sneezy, Sleepy, Happy,
Grumpy, Dopey, Doc, and Bashful.
Well, I'll be.
How did she do that?
My mother always taught me
that it was important to learn a
name.
Well, in order of the longest
toes to the shortest toes,
I have the longest toes.
If that helps.
And what exactly do you do
out here in the forest?
Oh. Well, it's our
job to mine the mines.
You'd be amazed at
what you can find.
Sparkling rocks of every kind.
A place where
magic still abides.
Not for long if she resides!
Look at the time.
The important thing is that Snow
White is out of harm's way at
our address.
- Right, fellas?
- Yeah.
-Absolutely.
-Objection.
Noted. Just ignore him.
Maybe I'll just
stay for one night.
One night. Then she leaves.
-You can come here.
-What size are your slippers?
-I love slumber parties.
-We got some spare upstairs.
You'll be safe
from the queen here.
Magic Mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest one of all?
Far beyond the castle wall,
somewhere in the woods dwells
Snow White,
fairest one of all.
No.
I am only bound by what is true.
The fairest lives.
She is not you.
♪ Seems we've hit
a little hiccup ♪
♪ Someone made a little mess ♪
♪ And who, of course,
is here to pick up ♪
♪ The pieces? ♪
♪ One guess ♪
♪ So, what's the treatment
For a traitor? ♪
♪ This craven coward of a man? ♪
♪ Diminish him ♪
♪ Then finish him ♪
♪ Because, well ♪
♪ I can ♪
You dare to disobey me?
I don't deserve mercy.
But if there's a drop
of it in your heart,
I beseech you,
show it to her.
♪ Perhaps I've been
a bit confusing ♪
♪ But I've no need
for your advice ♪
♪ In fact, I find
it quite amusing ♪
♪ Telling me to play nice! ♪
♪ Well, nice will
only get you nowhere ♪
♪ Nice won't get
the doing done ♪
♪ Ambitious girls must
be vicious girls ♪
♪ And, boy, they have fun! ♪
♪ This is gonna be fun! ♪
♪ All is fair when
you wear the crown ♪
♪ To be the queen
Means you do as you please ♪
♪ I could spare you ♪
♪ Or tear you right down ♪
♪ On a whim
I can bring the world to its
knees ♪
♪ Now, I could
forgive, even forget ♪
♪ Let you live,
you'd be all set ♪
♪ But to start, I
don't have the heart ♪
♪ As you might recall ♪
♪ So, darling, all is fair ♪
♪ When you're the
fairest of all ♪
♪ Now, perhaps you
have heard that ♪
♪ The truest of beauty
Will shine from inside ♪
♪ Well, if somebody said that ♪
♪ Somebody lied ♪
♪ It's the gold
and the glitter ♪
♪ And the gems and the jewels ♪
♪ Beauty means power ♪
♪ Means I write the rules ♪
♪ All is fair ♪
♪ When you wear the crown ♪
-♪ So who would dare stand in my
way? ♪ -♪ Stand in her way ♪
♪ Now, beware ♪
♪ If you let me down ♪
♪ Down, down, down ♪
-♪ In the dungeon you'll stay ♪
♪ But if you get the
deed finally done ♪
♪ I'll proceed, second to none ♪
♪ With no doubt when
I'm calling out ♪
-♪ "Mirror on the wall" ♪
-♪ Mirror on the wall ♪
♪ "Tell me, who is fair? ♪
♪ Who is fair beyond compare?" ♪
♪ It's gonna be me
that you declare ♪
Captain, search the forest.
Find Snow White
and don't come back without her.
♪ All is fair ♪
♪ When you're the fairest ♪
-♪ Of all ♪
-♪ Mirror on the wall ♪
♪ Who's the fairest
of them all? ♪
It's not fair.
It's the morning,
and she's still here.
They'll come looking for her,
and when they find her...
What do you have
to say about that?
- Now, Grumpy, you know Dopey
doesn't talk. -
Because he's a dope!
Just because his name is Dopey
doesn't mean he's
actually a dope.
Of course that's the reason.
Same as how you're called Happy
because you're happy.
And I'm called Grumpy
because I'm... I'm...
misunderstood.
Ow!
Shish kebabs!
Huh?
Here you go.
Hey!
Guys, let's all just
try to be friends.
Ow. Stop.
Hey! Yippee ki-yay!
-You're toast, mister!
-Aha!
Come here!
Settle down.
I'm gonna
get your long toe!
Grumpy, that tickles!
Oh...
- Oh, my foot!
- Huh?
Oh, no!
Pepper!
He's gonna blow.
Achoo!
Dopey,
breakfast is supposed
to go in your mouth.
Not on your head!
Isn't life gruel?
You get it? Gruel!
Are you all right?
Makes you want to run and hide.
Are you afraid to speak?
Oh.
Well, then, maybe we can start
with something small.
When I was a little girl,
my mother taught me how to
whistle.
So, even when I'm afraid to
speak, I whistle.
Because when you whistle,
it's your heart singing.
And that voice,
the one that's
hidden in your heart,
can be heard.
See? Now you try.
Well, just enough
to make a candle flicker.
Not go out.
You did it.
I knew you could.
Come on.
Hey! Come here.
Give it back!
I got it.
What's that divine
and ravishing noise?
Did a songbird come through a
window?
It's Dopey.
He sounds
like a baby angel.
It's a trick.
It's not a trick.
How are you doing that?
Well, you put your lips
together,
place your tongue behind your
teeth and whistle.
That's easy.
Is this normal,
or just something you do among
friends?
We're not friends.
275 years is a
long time to argue.
274.
Leave me out of it.
-I'm the only sensible one here.
-Oh.
And you feel like
they're not listening to sense?
Correct.
I take your point, Mr. Grumpy.
You... Wait.
What?
Well, it seems to me
that everyone here
could do a much better job
at listening to one another.
I was thinking the same thing.
Hey.
Uh, Miss White,
I wouldn't look in there if I...
She's really making herself at
home.
I don't remember those.
Now you wash the dishes.
You tidy up the room.
-Okay.
-Come on.
You clean those cobwebs.
And he'll use
the broom.
Me?
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
♪ And cheerfully together ♪
♪ We can tidy up the place ♪
♪ So hum a merry tune ♪
♪ It won't take long
when there's a song ♪
♪ To help you set the pace ♪
♪ And as you sweep the floor ♪
♪ What used to be a bore ♪
♪ Will feel just like a game ♪
♪ And not the same old chore
It was before ♪
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
You'll get it.
♪ When we're a team
The house will gleam ♪
♪ So whistle while you work ♪
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
♪ It's easy to get through it ♪
♪ When we do it hand in hand ♪
♪ So catch that merry tune ♪
I'll take it!
♪ When work is fun,
the work gets done ♪
♪ In half the time you planned ♪
♪ Wait! I think
that brush is mine ♪
♪ You shoulda hung a sign ♪
♪ If you don't hush
I'll take this brush ♪
♪ And shove it where
the sun don't shine ♪
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
♪ Your bickering
won't fix a thing ♪
♪ So, whistle while you work ♪
♪ It's easy to get through it
When we do it hand in hand ♪
Look at Dopey!
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
♪ We've scrubbed
the house together ♪
♪ Now it's clean
as clean can be ♪
♪ So, hum a merry tune ♪
♪ This grimy group
became a troupe ♪
♪ That feels like family ♪
♪ What used to be a mess ♪
♪ That lived at this address ♪
♪ Is now clean as a
whistle just from ♪
♪ Whistlin' sounds
of happiness ♪
♪ Whistle while you work ♪
♪ When work is fun,
the work gets done ♪
♪ It's mighty fine
when we combine ♪
♪ It won't take long
when there's a song ♪
♪ So whistle while you work ♪
I forgot getting along
could be so much fun.
I forgot we had an oven in here.
Well, when I was a little girl,
every day was like this.
Every day?
Every day.
When my father was king.
Oh.
The Huntsman said
the queen lied about my father.
She lied about everything.
What if he's still alive?
I have to find him.
You said that there were bandits
in the forest
who claimed to fight
in the king's name.
Human criminals.
Those rebels are
nothing but thieves.
They're actually
a band of erstwhile actors
whose sustenance
was made unstable
by the queen's greedy
economic policies
which forced them
into a liminal space
where ethics and
motives are ill-defined.
Well, where are they?
If they know the truth about my
father, I need to find them.
Oh, no. I advise against it.
It's too dangerous.
Stay with me.
I mean, us.
Yeah. You barely got away
from the queen the last time.
Gesundheit.
But this is what I have to do.
Besides, Grumpy's right.
The longer I stay here with you,
the more danger I put you in.
At last.
-Goodbye.
-Grumpy!
No.
It's time for me to stop hiding.
Thank you all
for showing me such kindness.
No, wait a minute.
Even you, Grumpy.
Now,
can you point me in
the right direction?
We're late for work!
Come on, everybody.
I need you to...
I'll get the snacks.
Come on, Sleepy. Hello?
Don't say a word.
You.
If we go this way,
we'll link up with the other
riders.
And when I told you
to come see what it was like out
here,
didn't expect you to bring
half the palace guards with you.
I didn't exactly invite them.
I had no choice but to run.
The queen wants me dead.
Come on.
I'm actually looking
for my father.
I was hoping you might
be able to help me.
You're loyal to
the one true king.
Right.
Absolutely.
We, uh...
We hear rumors, whispers.
Some people say he was taken
prisoner in the Southern
Kingdom, but...
You have no idea where he is.
I'm so sorry to disappoint.
You must have mistaken me
for a knight in shining armor.
I don't think anyone's
making that mistake.
I was hoping you
might know something.
Oh, of course.
Princesses are always waiting
for a prince to show up or a
king to come back.
My father is the only person who
can restore this kingdom to what
it once was.
A little late for
that, I'm afraid.
Obviously, you've forgotten
how things used to be,
when people were kind and fair.
I wish I had time
for things like
kindness and fairness.
Only problem is...
♪ Times are lookin' bleak ♪
♪ So, Princess, take a peek ♪
♪ See, every day
it's sink or swim ♪
♪ Famine's on the rise ♪
♪ With vultures
circling the skies ♪
♪ And prospects
Well, they're rather grim ♪
♪ Let me break you the news ♪
♪ The odds can't be beaten ♪
♪ And a man's gotta choose ♪
♪ Will he eat or get eaten? ♪
♪ Does that dampen your day? ♪
♪ Do the facts make you frown? ♪
♪ Wakin' up to the real world ♪
♪ Is bringin' you down? ♪
♪ Well, that sounds an awful lot
Like princess problems ♪
♪ Fin'lly learnin'
that life's not fair ♪
♪ Seems to me you got
Some princess problems ♪
♪ Ain't it crummy
When folks won't share? ♪
♪ I could try being "kind"
Or whatever you said ♪
♪ It's just that I'm partial
To not being dead ♪
♪ So I'm stickin' to my plan ♪
♪ Of grabbin' all I can ♪
♪ 'Stead of living
in a fantasy ♪
♪ See your princess problems
Don't apply to me ♪
So you've moved
on from potatoes?
I have many talents.
♪ Charming speech,
but are you done? ♪
♪ "None for all
and all for none" ♪
♪ Such a gift of
hope you give! ♪
♪ Yeah, well, hope's
in short supply ♪
♪ But, still, we have to try ♪
♪ Well, how about
we try to live? ♪
♪ So that's it? You give in? ♪
♪ Nah, you begin to get wise ♪
♪ 'Cause you can't fix the world
Baking apple pies ♪
♪ Yeah, we got a classic case
Of princess problems ♪
♪ The castle's cozy
But it's cold outside ♪
♪ Sure, just write 'em off
As princess problems ♪
♪ And stayin' selfish
is justified ♪
♪ That was harsh,
but I'm proud ♪
♪ Look at you, gettin' mean ♪
♪ Look, the kingdom needs help ♪
♪ You should go tell the queen ♪
♪ But I'm stayin' on the run ♪
♪ Lookin' out for number one ♪
♪ And that's the
way it's gonna be ♪
♪ 'Cause your princess problems
Don't apply to me ♪
Do not move, milady.
You're in the presence of the
rebel Quigg, master of the
crossbow.
Hands up!
Step away from our captain.
And no harm will come to you.
You don't have a crossbow.
- It was stolen.
- It's okay.
She's with me.
Captain?
And my associates.
Loyal to the king?
You're just a common criminal.
My name's Jonathan, Princess.
Not "Jonathan Princess."
Just "Jonathan..."
Princess.
Look...
♪ You seem a lovely gal ♪
♪ With your royal rationale ♪
♪ But out here in reality ♪
♪ See, your princess problems ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Apply ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ They don't apply to ♪
♪ Me ♪
Whoa!
It's the palace guards.
Two soldiers for
every one of us.
We are searching
for the Princess Snow White.
You have to run, Princess.
What about all of you?
Don't worry about us.
We'll hold them off.
-I'll fight with you.
-I'm not asking.
I'm making it a fair fight.
Yeah, the thing is,
I don't fight fair.
Don't shoot!
We can tell you where
the princess is.
Now.
I can't leave.
I'm going to need your help.
Last chance, bandits.
Tell us what you
know of Snow White.
You seek Snow White?
I'm over here.
This way.
- Go!
- Move!
Spread out!
Spread out. Find them.
Yes, sir!
Where's my horse?
Go, go.
You came back.
Someone had to solve
your princess problem.
I told you I'd fight with you.
- I guess you meant it.
- I guess so.
You continue to impress me.
Oh, thank you.
Compliment like that coming from
a criminal mastermind like
yourself.
Make sure we lost them.
The people,
they've forgotten
how it used to be.
And they despise the queen.
But they're afraid.
That's why we fight
in your father's name.
Your parents weren't
afraid of anything.
They made us all
feel a little braver.
They gave everyone hope.
Now, we'll cut
through to the glen a mile
south.
We need to cover our tracks.
- Jonathan?
-  -What was that?
Oh, no.
I think we have a bit of a
problem, Princess.
He's
going to need a doctor.
Doc is more of a sobriquet
rather than a technical title
as my true expertise lies
in the study of igneous,
sedimentary, and metamorphic
granules.
You know, rocks.
Oh!
I am the rebel Quigg,
master of the crossbow,
and I'm ordering
you to save him.
- Oh, we haven't even been
introduced yet. -
-In alphabetical order...
-Doc, please, we don't have
time.
He's badly injured.
You have to help.
But they're bandits!
-What are you gonna do about it?
-Come here, you.
This is exactly how the queen
would want us to behave.
Fighting with each other,
distrusting each other.
This is how she wins!
She's poisoned everyone into
believing that it's everyone for
themselves.
But if...
we can give up
our meager scraps,
we will inherit
what was meant for all of us.
And it's more than
any of us can imagine.
It just...
requires faith in each other.
Mmm.
Now help him.
Please.
Hmm.
Bring him inside.
Hot milk.
It helps me sleep.
Thank you.
I used the blast furnace
to cut through the bedrock,
then drilled to
the fissure core,
added a poultice or two.
A dose of acetum saturninum,
acid of sulfur dulcified.
Uh...
-Oh, oh!
-That was...
Huh.
- ...unpleasant.
- You did it, Doc.
I thought he was dead.
Hey.
-Thank you, Doc.
-Of course.
I would do anything
for Snow White's special friend.
- Ooh! You got a special
friend. -Oh, no.
- No.
- Oh.
- No. No.
- What?
- I would have brought anyone
here to... - Exactly.
Run-of-the-mill kindness.
It's nothing to do with you.
- Awkward.
- Oh, isn't this just wonderful?
You know what time
it is, fellas?
-Please, no.
-What time is it?
It's time to dance.
Yeah!
Ah, achoo!
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
You want to play cards?
No, thank you.
What about you?
Do you wanna play?
You and Maple are fine dancers.
Ah.
We're just friends.
Right.
You know, like you and Jonathan.
I'm pretty sure
Jonathan only cares about
himself.
Is that why he took
an arrow for ya?
What?
We all saw it.
That selfish, no-good thief?
He saved your life.
♪ I used to think that the way
Through the woods would be
lonely ♪
♪ Dark forest before me ♪
♪ The night hangin'
heavy above ♪
♪ And the wind blows ♪
♪ But now I don't
shake in the shadows ♪
♪ Maybe wherever
this road goes ♪
♪ I won't have to
walk it alone ♪
♪ 'Cause a hand meets a hand ♪
♪ Like it found where to land ♪
♪ And suddenly I've
Watched the world come alive ♪
♪ And now I'm lost in the view ♪
♪ So I start to let go ♪
♪ And give in to the glow ♪
♪ Oh, I know it's naive ♪
♪ But tonight I believe ♪
♪ That something so
good could come true ♪
♪ And maybe it might
have a little ♪
♪ Somethin' to do ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ I used to think that this
world Would forever stay broken♪
♪ Cutthroat and cruel ♪
♪ Every fool had to
fend for himself ♪
♪ But who knows? ♪
♪ When we're together
the time slows ♪
♪ Maybe, wherever
this road goes ♪
♪ I won't have to
walk it alone ♪
♪ 'Cause a hand meets a hand ♪
♪ Something I never planned ♪
♪ And suddenly I've
Watched the world come alive ♪
♪ And I just might
like the view ♪
♪ So I start to let go ♪
♪ Just to see what'll grow ♪
♪ And perhaps I'm naive ♪
♪ But tonight I believe ♪
♪ That something so
good could come true ♪
♪ And maybe it might
have a little ♪
♪ Somethin' to do ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ And maybe I'm dreaming ♪
♪ Well, I'd like to
stay just like this ♪
♪ But if there's a world ♪
♪ Where you wake me ♪
♪ Promise to wake me ♪
♪ With a kiss ♪
♪ A hand meets a hand ♪
♪ Fin'lly somewhere to land ♪
♪ Seems it's not so naive ♪
♪ To begin to believe ♪
♪ Something good has come true ♪
♪ And maybe it might
have a little ♪
♪ Something ♪
♪ It might have
everything to do ♪
♪ With you ♪
-Hi.
Soldiers.
- Oh, no.
- We have to leave.
- To protect the princess.
- Yes, Captain.
Achoo!
I can't let the queen's guard
find this place.
-I'm coming with you.
-No.
It's too dangerous.
You're the one they're looking
for.
I'll be back in two days.
And together
we'll go to the Southern Kingdom
and...
we'll find your father.
Well, here.
He gave this to me.
Take it for luck.
I can't accept this.
I'm not giving it to you.
I'm just giving you
reason to return.
Who fights in the
name of the king?
I!
Well, come on, then.
-Be safe.
-All right. Split up.
We'll lure the guards away
from the cottage.
Be careful out there!
Hey, thanks for having us.
Over here.
This way.
You're really doing
it, Johnny boy.
You're one of the good guys.
Honest, steadfast, loyal.
You're a...
idiot.
You look familiar.
Oh, yeah.
The lady with the good potatoes.
Where is Snow White?
Snow who?
You're protecting her.
Answer Her Majesty.
Show me where you found him.
In the forest,
two furlongs south
of the crossroads.
I'm sure you think you got this
licked, Your Majesty.
But trust me,
you don't know what
you're up against.
See, unlike you...
I know her.
I think you mean "knew."
I think it's time
for Snow White and I
to have a little talk.
♪ Banish any trace of beauty ♪
♪ Age me old as mummy dust ♪
♪ Do your dark,
bewitching duty ♪
♪ Sweet potion ♪
♪ You must ♪
♪ A voice as creaky
as a cackle ♪
♪ A hunching hag
with wrinkled skin ♪
♪ A mane of white ♪
♪ A flash of fright ♪
♪ My plan ♪
♪ Can ♪
♪ Begin ♪
"Poison apple. The
sleeping death."
Hmm.
"Antidote."
"True love's kiss."
That
won't get you free.
♪ Just one bite, juicy and red ♪
♪ Then good night,
put her to bed ♪
♪ Claim your prize
If you wanna rise, someone's
gotta fall ♪
♪ Darling, all is fair ♪
♪ When you're the fairest ♪
♪ Of all ♪
I don't like it.
It's too dangerous with the
queen's guard out there looking
for you.
We could come with you.
Do you really have to go?
I need to find the
truth about my father.
If there's any
chance he's alive...
And when you find
what you're looking for,
you'll come back...
right?
I will.
I promise.
Okay.
Come on, fellas. Let's go.
Jonathan?
I'm sorry, my dear.
Did I frighten you?
No, I was expecting
someone else.
Can I help you?
It is I who can help you.
Are you Snow White?
The princess?
Who did you say you were?
I have come with a message.
From Jonathan.
From Jonathan?
I'm afraid he's been captured
by the queen.
Captured? No.
He gave me this necklace.
He said you'd know
what it means.
I need to go to him.
But what of the danger?
Ah. You love him?
Well,
because love is so precious,
I will help you.
Here.
Take this apple
to sustain you on the road.
Hey!
Whoa!
Snow White.
I remember how generous your
father was to his people.
That's why it is an honor for me
to return the favor to his
daughter.
I know I don't have
much to give...
but giving you this apple
makes me feel as though
his spirit is here.
Come on! Hyah!
Thank you.
For him.
For your father.
Hyah! Hyah!
-Go. Come on!
-Faster!
What's happening?
Something's wrong.
I did know your father.
Quite well.
What do you mean?
I knew he was a fool!
You. It's you.
It was almost too easy for me
to have him killed.
His goodness cost
him his throne,
as it will cost you your life.
So...
tell me, Snow White...
...who is the
fairest one of all?
Your envious heart can be at
rest.
You, my Queen,
are fairest of all.
All hail the queen,
fairest of them all.
You've
done this every day.
It hasn't moved.
Forget it.
I did forget.
I forgot what it
was to have courage,
to have hope, but then...
then I met Snow White.
She fought for us.
With us.
When she had every
reason to run.
She never gave up on us.
I am not...
giving up on her.
-Come on.
-Pull harder.
Listen, the queen's secret
entrance lets out one mile
from the royal stables
where there's dozens of horses.
I'll check for guards. You go.
Good luck.
Whoa.
I'm so sorry.
Snow White...
-Ah.
-She's alive!
-She's awake.
-It's a miracle.
Jonathan.
What is it?
Hey, what's wrong?
My father...
He's gone forever.
Murdered by the queen.
Oh, dear.
What will we do now?
♪ My father told me ♪
♪ Long ago ♪
♪ I braved a bitter
storm of snow ♪
♪ I have to know ♪
♪ Does that girl
still live in me? ♪
♪ Mother, Father won't return ♪
♪ They left a wish
for me to learn ♪
♪ That this kingdom is my ♪
♪ Destiny ♪
♪ Time to rise
and lift my head ♪
♪ Time to lead and not be led ♪
♪ To be the girl ♪
♪ I always said ♪
♪ I'd be ♪
It's time.
Time?
Time to restore our kingdom.
It won't be easy.
She'll do everything
she can to stop us.
Let her try.
Did he... Was that...
Dopey?
We're not afraid.
Dopey.
Not anymore.
Oh, wow.
Well said, Dopey.
Then neither am I.
Follow me.
Shh!
- On to the main gate!
- Yes, sir.
♪ No more sending
whispers to the water ♪
♪ 'Cause you're everything ♪
♪ You were wishing
and waiting for ♪
♪ Someone fearless ♪
♪ Someone fair ♪
♪ Someone brave ♪
♪ Someone true ♪
I believe you're looking for me.
As a matter of fact,
I believe it is you
who's looking for me.
Stand aside.
This is my father's house.
You killed him.
You stole it from
him, from all of us.
And now we're here
to take it back.
Pretty...
isn't she?
Delicate, elegant, exquisite.
You think you want a flower.
But a flower wilts.
A flower cannot keep you safe.
Or raise an army,
or lead a kingdom.
A flower cannot give you
what I can give you.
Perfection.
Power.
Beauty.
If you want the throne...
take it.
They're waiting.
Enough of this charade.
Guards, hold her.
You.
Let the people watch her die.
Paul.
You were a farmer.
In the Western Vale.
You have a wife.
Eleanor.
You had a grove of cherry trees
and when they would blossom,
you would invite the village
to come and pick them.
To share them.
Matthew.
You were a baker...
just like your father.
You never turned anyone away
if they were hungry,
even if they didn't have
a coin left in their pocket.
Arthur.
Enough.
William.
I remember you.
All of you.
I said, "Enough!"
There was a time where
we lived with hope.
When good things were nurtured
and allowed to grow.
I remember.
Do you?
And I.
Leave.
Now.
And never come back.
I am the rebel Quigg,
master of the crossbow.
No.
It isn't true.
Look at me. I'm
still the fairest.
Famed is thy beauty.
But it goes no
further than the skin.
For Snow White,
beauty comes from deep within.
And so, my Queen,
at last, you see.
She will always be
more fair than thee.
You lie!
Snow White
more fair than thee.
Once upon a time,
there was a peaceful kingdom
governed by a virtuous queen
who believed
that the true beauty of her land
was not to be measured
in gems or jewels,
but in its people.
The queen ruled with
kindness and love.
She was fearless,
fair, brave and true.
And her name was Snow White.
♪ From
the mountains high ♪
-♪ To the deepest mines ♪
-♪ To the deepest of mines ♪
-♪ In a golden sky ♪
-♪ Oh, how the kingdom shines ♪
♪ And the strongest of roots
Bear the sweetest of fruits ♪
♪ For we reap what we sow ♪
♪ By the lessons we know ♪
♪ And the bounty will flow ♪
♪ Where the good things grow ♪
♪ From the mountains high ♪
♪ In a golden sky ♪
♪ Where the good things grow ♪